var quiz = [{"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Many historians and economists view the Enclosure Laws in England in the 1780s and 1820s as a significant step toward modern capitalism."}, {"answers": ["Underproduction and overconsumption", "Overproduction and underconsumption", "Overproduction and over consumption", "Underproduction and underconsumption"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Overaccumulation leads to what two things?"}, {"answers": ["Give tax rebates", "Federal regulations to encourage saving.", "\u201cNew Deal\u201d policies", "Putting out-of-work people to work on public projects, like the CCC"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following would NOT be a response to underconsumption?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Most environmental activists are men."}, {"answers": ["A commodity doesn\u2019t have value.", "A commodity is something that can be bought or sold.", "A commodity is nature plus labor.", "A commodity is produced by labor."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is NOT true regarding commodities?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Prior to capitalism, good were sold at their exchange rate."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Hazardous materials are placed in minority and low-income neighborhoods because these groups often have less power to protest."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Moving a factory from Mexico to Vietnam is an example of the spatial fix."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "According to Marx, problems such as overaccumulation, overproduction, and underconsumption are anomalies in capitalism and suggest that the system is not functioning properly."}, {"answers": ["surplus value", "the means of production", "crises", "exchange value"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "In order to create _______ in a capitalist economy, workers and the environment must be undervalued."}, {"answers": ["Environmental regulations are more lax in poorer countries.", "Environmental regulations are often not enforced in poorer countries.", "All of the choices are correct.", "Disposal costs are less in poorer countries."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Why do we export millions of tons of hazardous waste to poorer countries each year?"}, {"answers": ["The means of production", "Commodities", "Surplus value", "The conditions of production"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "_______ are the raw materials needed to produce things, such as wood, iron, and oil."}, {"answers": ["Move jobs to \u201ccheaper\u201d places, like developing countries.", "Have workers work longer hours for less pay.", "Invoke pay increases for laborers.", "Exploit natural resources."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a method for capitalists to maintain accumulation of wealth?"}, {"answers": ["Accumulation of capital", "Accumulation of natural resources", "Accumulation of workers", "Accumulation of pollution"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "When Marx writes about \u201caccumulation\u201d, what is he referring to?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "According to social reproduction, unhealthy workers are more productive workers."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Environmental justice is primarily concerned with the uneven distribution of environmental \u201cbads.\u201d"}, {"answers": ["primitive accumulation", "uneven development", "the spatial fix", "globalism"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The Enclosure Laws were an example of _______."}, {"answers": ["Clean Air Act", "Cap and Trade", "Emissions taxes", "Kyoto Protocol"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which current policy promotes the global trade of pollution?"}, {"answers": ["Helps bring awareness of nature", "Immerses people in nature", "Commodifies nature", "Supports \u201c green companies\u201d"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Purchasing products that are related to nature does what NEGATIVE thing to nature?"}, {"answers": ["It does not help us approach problems with non-human entities.", "Defers environmental activism until after economic problems are solved.", "None of the other choices: These are all problems with the political economy perspective.", "Focuses on capitalism at the expense of other social and ecological relationships."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a problem with the political economy perspective?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Development is always uneven."}, {"answers": ["The second contradiction of capitalism", "The first contradiction of capitalism", "Private accumulation", "Globalism"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "_______ describes how capitalism undermines itself by undermining the environmental conditions necessary for its own perpetuation."}, {"answers": ["eco-feminist", "institutionalist", "market environmentalist", "political economy"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "The _______ perspective is mostly concerned with identifying how power relationships and economic systems produce environmental and social conditions."}, {"answers": ["Poor people would rather have economic development than a clean environment.", "There would be fewer earnings losses to pollute in a poorer country.", "Poor countries have more land to redistribute the pollution.", "Some countries are under-polluted, so they should absorb their fair share."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following statements (in the memo written by Lawrence Summers) was NOT used to justify the export of polluting industries to poorer countries?"}, {"answers": ["When workers are paid more than minimum wage.", "Over local vs. global acquisitions.", "Contradictions occur over humans vs. nature.", "When capital becomes over-concentrated."], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "According to Marx, when does a \u201ccontradiction\u201d occur?"}, {"answers": ["Social reproduction", "Socialism", "Overproduction", "Overaccumulation"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "When people speak of the\u201dTop 1%\u201d, they are referring to a term in economics known as:"}, {"answers": ["Accumulation", "Crisis", "Labor", "Nature"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Marx\u2019s concepts of all of the following things, EXCEPT what, explain how the economy produces environmental problems."}, {"answers": ["Overaccumulation", "Primitive accumulation", "The \u201cCommons\u201d", "Conditions of production"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The enclosure and privatization of previously communal resources is known as:"}, {"answers": ["Environmental problems are eliminated by the principles that govern capitalism.", "Poorer countries cause environmental problems because they don\u2019t enforce environmental laws.", "Environmental problems are already built into the economy that causes them.", "Only multi-national corporations can be blamed for environmental problems."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Marx would agree with which of the following statements about modern capitalism and environmental problems?"}, {"answers": ["Means of production", "Production of nature", "Conditions of production", "Social reproduction"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Raw materials, used to produce commodities, are called what?"}]

quizCollection['7'] = quiz
